<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<section id="2584">
  <number>0</number>
  <name></name>
  <summary>&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;img src="@@PLUGINFILE@@/Circle%20Hands%20%281%29.png" alt="Hands forming a circle" width="150" height="150" role="presentation" class="atto_image_button_text-bottom" /&gt;Welcome to &lt;span style="font-size: 2rem;"&gt;Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion: From Awareness to Action &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The American Institutes for Research developed this course and the accompanying materials with contributions from Elevation Educational Consulting Group, Lisa Lord Consulting, Aricles “Wulf” James, and Fatima Marcial. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose: &lt;/strong&gt;You are encouraged to begin this course from a perspective of empathy and an intent to gain understanding. This applies to empathy for students, colleagues, and yourself. Thinking through how to address DEI concerns as you uncover them can feel overwhelming. If you feel overwhelmed, take a break for a few hours or days, and return to the course when you feel prepared to continue. Be sure to give yourself grace if you identify an area of growth. As humans, we are all imperfect beings continuously learning and growing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can take this course individually or with a group; those participating as part of a group will receive specific instructions on select activities. Groups are encouraged as it allows you to develop a shared understanding with your colleagues and feel supported while learning about DEI. However, it is essential to remember empathy while completing this course with a group—lead collaborative discussions around DEI with kindness, compassion, and empathy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is recommended to complete this course one unit at a time (e.g., one unit per week) to give yourself time to process the information you are learning and complete all recommended activities. Additionally, if you are taking this course with a group, completing the course one section at a time allows you to discuss the content by unit and reflect together on what you are learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Commitment:&lt;/strong&gt; This course will take approximately 6 hours to complete. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectives: &lt;/strong&gt;This course is leading you toward conducting an equity audit. Classroom equity audits can be conducted and followed through independently or in a group; however, a program equity audit requires participation and buy-in from staff. If you intend to conduct a program equity audit or group classroom equity audit, please be sure to take time to prepare staff by holding small group conversations in advance. See Unit 5 for more details on how to prepare staff for an equity audit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;fter completing this course, you will be able to:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li class="O0"&gt;Understand and define what is meant by diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) in the classroom and program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="O0"&gt;Identify steps individuals can take to advance their commitment to DEI progressively from both an individual and a programmatic perspective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="O0"&gt;Identify steps for conducting an equity audit and work toward the sustainability of DEI efforts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;This course is composed of the following units:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introduction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Units 1–5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class="O1" style="margin-left: 60px;"&gt;Unit 1: Understanding and Defining DEI&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="O1" style="margin-left: 60px;"&gt;Unit 2: Awareness Building: Understanding Adult Learners&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="O1" style="margin-left: 60px;"&gt;Unit 3: Awareness Building: Cultural Competence and Inclusion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="O1" style="margin-left: 60px;"&gt;Unit 4: Awareness Building: The Many Forms of Bias&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="O1" style="margin-left: 60px;"&gt;Unit 5: Taking Action: Equity Audit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conclusion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the main course page. Each unit of the course below includes downloadable and printable resources, activities for reflection, and resource lists with links to websites, videos, and other materials to enhance your learning experience. Please note: Items with solid boxes can be self-checked to indicate completion; however, all assessments are graded and required for completion. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: This course was developed under contract with the American Institutes for Research (AIR) with funding from the U.S. Department of Education (ED), Office of Career, Technical, and Adult Education (OCTAE), under Contract No. 91990020F0340. The content and opinions expressed herein do not necessarily represent the positions or policies of the U.S. Department of Education, and no official endorsement by the U.S. Department of Education should be inferred.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To begin, select “Course Introduction” below.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</summary>
  <summaryformat>1</summaryformat>
  <sequence>9297</sequence>
  <visible>1</visible>
  <availabilityjson>{"op":"&amp;","c":[],"showc":[]}</availabilityjson>
  <timemodified>1665673395</timemodified>
</section>